

Stefani Danailovska

Customer Support Specialist

ul. Bul. Makedonska Vojska 10/1-12, Gjorche Petrov,

+389 75 225 899 stefani.danailovska@gmail.com

Summary

Dynamic and motivated Customer Support Specialist with a proven record in digital communication, customer support, and social media. Strong decision-making, creativity, and problem-solving skills. Fluent English speaker, excellent written English, with $out standing\ communication\ skills.$

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- Customer Service/Support
- Teamwork
- Communication
- Adaptability
- Fast LearnerCreative Thinking
- Hard Working
- Good Team Player

EDUCATION HISTORY

Faculty of Economics, SS. Cyril and Methodius University, Skopje Bachelor of E-Business October 2017 - November 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Support Specialist at Vita Media Group, Skopje February 2023 - Present

- Answering all the questions and concerns on chat Freshdesk
- Providing support for the users for all the issues they
- might have

 Daily testing of the EP pages for broken links, and text
- Monthly crediting of bonus packages
- Monthly sending Trustpilot offers to satisfied customers Posting on Social Media channels
- Facebook manual invitation to the valuable users
- Monitoring and resolving customer complaints on social media and chat
- Informing customers about new offers, features, functionalities

PR and Digital Communications Specialist at Vita Media Group, Skopje November 2021 – February 2023

- Creating content calendars for Social Media
- Writing creative content for the company and the products across different social media channels
- Writing news for the website
- Website Administration WordPress activities
- Writing internal newslettersHelping with the office activities

Digital Marketing Intern at Kara5, Skopje June 2021 – October 2021

- Creating content calendars for Social Media
- Market and keyword research analysis
- Setting Google Ads campaignsCompetitor analysis
- On-site SEO analysis

Digital Marketing Intern at Kares Group, Skopje March 2021 - May 2021

- Creating Social Media Content and organizing profiles on Instagram and Facebook
- Website Administration WordPress activities

Digital Marketing Intern at Axeltra, Skopje November 2020 – February 2021

- Lead generation Gathering data regarding
- the potential customers and their competitors

 Working on Marketing Plan Goal: Get one client by the end of june

Sales Assistant at DM - Drogerie Markt October 2020 - November 2020

- Communication with customers and their
- needs on a daily basis

 Helping customers to buy what they want and

Front Desk at Berkeley Oceanfront Hotel, New Jersey, USA June 2019 – September 2019

- Everyday communication with customers and their needs
- Solving daily problems in the hotel
- Always making customers feel welcome

Sales Assistant at Mayfair Fast Food Restaurant, New Jersey, USA June 2019 - September 2019

- Communication with customers and their needs on a daily basis
- Always making customers happy with their

Intern at Komercijalna Banka, Skopje August 2018 - September 2018

 Sorting documents in the alphabetical order on the daily basis

Sales Promoter at MPG Solutions Part-time

• Promoting new products to the customers

LANGUAGES

English В2

COURSES